$CapacityOverhaulNG	Capacity Overhaul NG
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_PAGE	Toggle Mod Features
$CONG_BaseValues_PAGE	Adjust Base Values
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_PAGE	Buffs and Debuffs
$CONG_WeightModifiers_PAGE	Weight Modifiers
$CONG_Debug_PAGE	Debug

$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_HEADER	Toggle Capacity Features
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_HEADER	Toggle Weight Features
$CONG_BaseValues_Capacity_HEADER	Adjust Capacity Values
$CONG_BaseValues_Items_HEADER	Adjust Item Capacity Categories
$CONG_BaseValues_Weight_HEADER	Adjust Weight Values
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_HEADER	Configure Speed Effects
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_HEADER	Configure Combat Effects
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_HEADER	Configure Stamina Drain
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_HEADER	Configure Stamina Regeneration
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_HEADER	Configure Stealth Effects
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Races_HEADER	Per-Race Carry Weight Modifiers
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_HEADER	Stamina-based Carry Weight Modifiers
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_HEADER	Level-based Carry Weight Modifiers

$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_NoHands_TEXT	Disable Hands While Over Capacity
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_NoHands_INFO	While over capacity, prevent the player from unsheathing hands or weapons. Does not prevent interactions or picking up items.
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_NoPickup_TEXT	Prevent Item Pickup While Over Capacity
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_NoPickup_INFO	While over capacity, prevent the player from picking up any new items. Will not affect items added by other means (i.e. Quest rewards, etc.)
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_SkillsAffect_TEXT	Skills Affect Capacity Limits
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Capacity_SkillsAffect_INFO	Some capacity categories (Alchemy, Ammo, etc.) will increase alongside certain player skills.
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_VanillaLimit_TEXT	Use Vanilla Carry Weight Limit
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_VanillaLimit_INFO	While enabled, the player's base carry weight will remain static, equivalent to the default carry limit (Vanilla = 300, Survival = 150, Or whatever your mod setup may have changed it to) and unaffected by any modifiers from this mod. Effectively returns vanilla functionality - normal game effects (Steed stone, enchantments, etc.) will continue to apply as normal.
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_StaminaAffects_TEXT	Max Stamina Affects Weight Limit
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_StaminaAffects_INFO	Player's maximum stamina will be considered during the calculation of the max carry weight limit. This includes ALL sources, both permanent (such as stamina boosts from levelling up) and temporary (such as enchantments and potions).
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_LevelAffects_TEXT	Player Level Affects Weight Limit
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_LevelAffects_INFO	Player's level will be considered during the calculation of the max carry weight limit.
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_RaceAffects_TEXT	Player Race Affects Weight Limit
$CONG_ToggleFeatures_Weight_RaceAffects_INFO	Player's race will be considered during the calculation of the max carry weight limit.

$CONG_BaseValues_LargeCap_TEXT	Large Item Capacity
$CONG_BaseValues_LargeCap_INFO	Adjust the limit placed on the amount of large items you can hold before being considered over-capacity. Storage capacity is shared between all standard categories (that is, tiny, small, medium, and large items, but not alchemy, ammo, or coins) - i.e. carrying an amount of large items equal to this value will not put you over-capacity, but proceeding to pick up a single tiny item will.
$CONG_BaseValues_MediumPerLarge_TEXT	Medium Items Per Large Item
$CONG_BaseValues_MediumPerLarge_INFO	Choose how many medium items are required to fill the same amount of carry capacity as one large item.
$CONG_BaseValues_SmallPerMedium_TEXT	Small Items Per Medium Item
$CONG_BaseValues_SmallPerMedium_INFO	Choose how many small items are required to fill the same amount of carry capacity as one medium item.
$CONG_BaseValues_TinyPerSmall_TEXT	Tiny Items Per Small Item
$CONG_BaseValues_TinyPerSmall_INFO	Choose how many tiny items are required to fill the same amount of carry capacity as one small item. 
$CONG_BaseValues_AlchemyCap_TEXT	Alchemy Capacity
$CONG_BaseValues_AlchemyCap_INFO	Adjust the limit placed on the amount of alchemy items (potions and poisons) you can hold before overflowing into standard storage. Once this limit is reached, alchemy items will overflow into standard storage and fill the same amount of space (per unit) as tiny items.
$CONG_BaseValues_AmmoCap_TEXT	Ammo Capacity
$CONG_BaseValues_AmmoCap_INFO	Adjust the limit placed on the amount of ammo (arrows and bolts) you can hold before overflowing into standard storage. Once this limit is reached, ammo will overflow into standard storage and fill the same amount of space (per unit) as tiny items.
$CONG_BaseValues_CoinCap_TEXT	Coin Capacity
$CONG_BaseValues_CoinCap_INFO	Adjust the limit placed on the amount of coins you can hold before overflowing into standard storage.
$CONG_BaseValues_CoinsPerTiny_TEXT	Coins Per Tiny Item
$CONG_BaseValues_CoinsPerTiny_INFO	Choose how many overflowed coins are required to fill the same amount of carry capacity as one tiny item. This value is only applicable when the amount of coins held exceeds the coin capacity limit, at which point any overflowing coins will begin to fill standard storage.

$CONG_BaseValues_LargeItemWeight_TEXT	Large Item Minimum Weight
$CONG_BaseValues_LargeItemWeight_INFO	Items weighing this much (or more) will be considered a large item for capacity purposes. WARNING: VALUE MUST BE LARGER THAN MEDIUM AND SMALL ITEM WEIGHT SETTINGS (below).
$CONG_BaseValues_MediumItemWeight_TEXT	Medium Item Minimum Weight
$CONG_BaseValues_MediumItemWeight_INFO	Items weighing this much (or more) will be considered a medium item for capacity purposes. WARNING: VALUE MUST BE LARGER THAN SMALL ITEM WEIGHT SETTING (below)
$CONG_BaseValues_SmallItemWeight_TEXT	Small Item Minimum Weight
$CONG_BaseValues_SmallItemWeight_INFO	Items weighing this much (or more) will be considered a small item for capacity purposes. Items weighing less than this will be considered tiny items.

$CONG_BaseValues_BaseWeight_TEXT	Base Carry Weight
$CONG_BaseValues_BaseWeight_INFO	Adjust the player's base carry weight limit. The in-game value will likely be different, as any modifiers you have enabled in settings will be applied to this value.

$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_Toggle_TEXT	Weight Affects Movement Speed
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_Toggle_INFO	Determines whether the weight of items held should affect the player's movement speed, relative to the actual weight limit. The modifiers below adjust the severity of the positive and negative effects.
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_ModPos_TEXT	Positive Speed Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_ModPos_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_ModNeg_TEXT	Negative Speed Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Speed_ModNeg_INFO

$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_Toggle_TEXT	Weight Affects Combat Abilities
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_Toggle_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_ModPos_TEXT	Positive Combat Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_ModPos_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_ModNeg_TEXT	Negative Combat Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Combat_ModNeg_INFO

$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_Toggle_TEXT	Weight Affects Stealth 
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_Toggle_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_ModPos_TEXT	Positive Stealth Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_ModPos_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_ModNeg_TEXT	Negative Stealth Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_Stealth_ModNeg_INFO

$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_Toggle_TEXT	Weight Affects Stamina Drain
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_Toggle_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_ModPos_TEXT	Positive Drain Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_ModPos_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_ModNeg_TEXT	Negative Drain Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamDrain_ModNeg_INFO

$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_Toggle_TEXT	Weight Affects Stamina Regeneration
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_Toggle_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_ModPos_TEXT	Positive Regen Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_ModPos_INFO
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_ModNeg_TEXT	Negative Regen Modifier
$CONG_BuffsDebuffs_StamRegen_ModNeg_INFO

$CONG_Debug_ToggleMod_TEXT	Disable/Enable Mod
$CONG_Debug_ToggleMod_INFO	Disables or Enables all features of the mod, including all adjusted values and effects applied to the player.
$CONG_Debug_LogContainerEvents_TEXT	Enable Container Events In Log
$CONG_Debug_LogContainerEvents_INFO	Will print all container events (i.e. an item moving from one NPC/container/worldspace to another) into this mod's log file.
$CONG_Debug_LogOnlyPlayerContainerEvents_TEXT	Only Print Player Container Events
$CONG_Debug_LogOnlyPlayerContainerEvents_INFO	Will restrict the container event logger to only print container events involving the player.
$CONG_Debug_LogLoadEvents_TEXT	Enable Load Events In Log
$CONG_Debug_LogLoadEvents_INFO	Will print all game load events into this mod's log file.
$CONG_Debug_LogMenuEvents_TEXT	Enable Menu Events In Log
$CONG_Debug_LogMenuEvents_INFO	Will print all menu open and close events into this mod's log file.
$CONG_Debug_LogOnlyRelevantMenuEvents_TEXT	Only Print Relevant Menu Events
$CONG_Debug_LogOnlyRelevantMenuEvents_INFO	Will restrict the menu event logger to only print menu events utilised by this mod's functions.
$CONG_Debug_LogEquipEvents_TEXT	Enable Equip Events In Log
$CONG_Debug_LogEquipEvents_INFO	Will print all equip/unequip events into this mod's log file.
$CONG_Debug_LogOnlyPlayerEquipEvents_TEXT	Only Print Player Equip Events
$CONG_Debug_LogOnlyPlayerEquipEvents_INFO	Will restrict the equip event logger to only print equip events involving the player.

$CONG_WeightModifiers_DefaultRace_TEXT	Default/Fallback
$CONG_WeightModifiers_DefaultRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight. NOTE: The "Default" race modifier is only used when the player's race is not identified by the mod. The most likely reason for this is a custom player race.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_AltmerRace_TEXT	Altmer
$CONG_WeightModifiers_AltmerRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_ArgonianRace_TEXT	Argonian
$CONG_WeightModifiers_ArgonianRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_BosmerRace_TEXT	Bosmer
$CONG_WeightModifiers_BosmerRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_BretonRace_TEXT	Breton
$CONG_WeightModifiers_BretonRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_DunmerRace_TEXT	Dunmer
$CONG_WeightModifiers_DunmerRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_ImperialRace_TEXT	Imperial
$CONG_WeightModifiers_ImperialRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_KhajiitRace_TEXT	Khajiit
$CONG_WeightModifiers_KhajiitRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_NordRace_TEXT	Nord
$CONG_WeightModifiers_NordRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_OrcRace_TEXT	Orc
$CONG_WeightModifiers_OrcRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_RedguardRace_TEXT	Redguard
$CONG_WeightModifiers_RedguardRace_INFO	Adjust the race-based modifier to be utilised in the calculation of the player's carry weight.

$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_Modifier_TEXT	Bonus Balance Modifier
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_Modifier_INFO	Allows for fine-tuning the final bonus carry weight granted based on stamina, if the bonus is enabled. Can also be used to fine-tune the balance between the stamina and level-based bonuses, such as to give one of them more of an impact relative to the other, without having to adjust other settings.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_TempAddsWeight_TEXT	Temporary Stamina Adds Carry Weight
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_TempAddsWeight_INFO	Choose whether temporary buffs to stamina should also increase carry weight while they are active. This (to my knowledge) includes enchantments and potions, but not blessings, ingredients, plus a few other miscellaneous stamina sources. Stamina gained via levelling up will affect the carry weight bonus regardless of this setting.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_Simple_TEXT	Simple Weight Bonus Calculation
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_Simple_INFO	ENABLED: Use a simple, linear method to calculate the carry weight bonus, with the rate defined by the setting below. DISABLED: Use a complex method, which can be tuned to a high degree to provide a carry weight bonus that increases non-linearly to the user's specifications.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_WeightPer_TEXT	Carry Weight Per Stamina
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_WeightPer_INFO	Only used when Simple Calculation is ENABLED. Will grant the value chosen for this setting for each point of stamina the player has. Note that this is based on the player's stamina limit (and does not consider consumed stamina), and a carry weight bonus will only be granted for stamina points above the base stamina of 100.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_ComplexRate_TEXT	Complex Rate
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_ComplexRate_INFO	Negative values result in diminishing returns, with a faster increase to the carry weight bonus at lower stamina points that slows down as the player's stamina limit increases. Positive values result in the opposite, where the bonus will grow larger per stamina point the higher the player's stamina gets.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_ComplexPivot_TEXT	Complex Pivot Point
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Stamina_ComplexPivot_INFO	Mostly just a way to fine-tune the growth rate of the equation, but a rough guideline is that this value + 100 will be approximate to the stamina limit at which the carry weight bonus will be +25% of the base carry weight.

$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_Modifier_TEXT	Bonus Balance Modifier
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_Modifier_INFO	Allows for fine-tuning the final bonus carry weight granted based on level, if the bonus is enabled. Can also be used to fine-tune the balance between the stamina and level-based bonuses, such as to give one of them more of an impact relative to the other, without having to adjust other settings.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_Simple_TEXT	Simple Weight Bonus Calculation
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_Simple_INFO	ENABLED: Use a simple, linear method to calculate the carry weight bonus, with the rate defined by the setting below. DISABLED: Use a complex method, which can be tuned to a high degree to provide a carry weight bonus that increases non-linearly to the user's specifications.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_WeightPer_TEXT	Carry Weight Per Level
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_WeightPer_INFO	Only used when Simple Calculation is ENABLED. Will grant the value chosen for this setting for each level the player has.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_ComplexRate_TEXT	Complex Rate
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_ComplexRate_INFO	Negative values result in diminishing returns, with a faster increase to the carry weight bonus at lower levels that slows down as the player's level increases. Positive values result in the opposite, where the bonus will grow larger per level the higher the player's level gets.
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_ComplexPivot_TEXT	Complex Pivot Point
$CONG_WeightModifiers_Level_ComplexPivot_INFO	Mostly just a way to fine-tune the growth rate of the equation, but a rough guideline is that this value will be approximate to the level at which the carry weight bonus will be +50% of the base carry weight.